<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE task PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA Task//EN" "technicalContent/dtd/task.dtd" [
]>



<task id = "id168DF0T0TNL"><title>Applying Grease to Lock Pins and
Set Screws</title>
<prolog><author>anamika sharma</author></prolog>
<taskbody><steps><step><cmd>Gather four Lock Pins (C6) and apply
Silicon Moly Blend or Pro-Long EP2 Plus grease to their threads.</cmd></step>
<step><cmd>Engage each of the four Lock Pins (C6) to the mating
threads through the Retaining Ring (C4). Fully tighten them with
the appropriate size Hex Key (Level 3 Hold Point).<image href =
"../Images/Lock_Pins.png"  height = "271.500pt" width = "281.250pt"
/></cmd></step>
<step><note><p>Stop the hoist in position to install the four Lock
Pins (C6).</p></note>
<cmd>Use a chain wrench to disengage the Retaining Ring (C4) from
the mating threads on the Lower Sub (C2). Have an assistant to hold
the Lower Sub (C2) with a second chain wrench if the hoist does
not prevent it from spinning.</cmd></step>
<step><cmd>Lower the Retaining Ring (C4) to rest on the shoulder
of the Upper Sub (C1).</cmd></step>
<step><cmd>Gather the External K-Seal (101901881), two Back-up Rings (102001446),
and an O-Ring (102001451).</cmd></step>
<step><cmd>Apply a thin layer of Silicon Moly Blend or Pro-Long
EP2 Plus grease to the K-Seal (101901881), O-Ring (102001451), and
Back-up Ring (102001446) and install them in the correct location
according to the General Assembly Drawing, see figures below (Level
3 Hold Point).<image href = "../Images/Apply_Grease.png"  height
= "433.500pt" width = "360.749pt" /><image href = "../Images/Install.png"
 height = "396.000pt" width = "342.000pt" /></cmd></step>
<step><cmd>Fix two appropriate size chain wrenches on the OD of
the Retaining Ring (C4) at 180° apart.</cmd></step>
<step><cmd>With an assistant at the other chain wrench, evenly lift
the Retaining Ring (C4) and turn it in the clockwise direction,
simultaneously, in order to engage it to the mating threads on the
Lower Sub (C2), see figure below.<image href = "../Images/RetainingRing_LowerSub.png"
 height = "312.000pt" width = "285.000pt" /></cmd></step>
<step><note><p>Do not allow any cross threading since it is necessary
to manage the Retaining Ring’s weight while trying to get the threads
engaged.</p></note>
<cmd>Gather four Set Screws (C7) and apply Silicon Moly Blend or
Pro-Long EP2 Plus grease to their threads.</cmd></step>
<step><cmd>Engage one of the four Set Screws (C7) to the mating
threads on the Load Ring (C3).</cmd></step>
<step><cmd>Repeat the previous step for the remaining three Set
Screws (C7) that are set 90° apart, see figure below.<image href
= "../Images/Set_Screws.png"  height = "301.500pt" width = "279.000pt"
/></cmd></step>
<step><cmd>Use the hoist and Cloth Slings to orient the assembly
horizontally and install the Lower Sub Thread Protector (101901880)
and the Upper Sub Thread Protector (101901879) if necessary.</cmd></step></steps>
<postreq><ol><li><p>Complete the Maintenance Check Sheet.</p></li>
<li><p>Label the equipment per Global Maintenance Standards.</p></li>
<li><p>Store the equipment according to Global Maintenance Standards.</p></li></ol></postreq></taskbody></task>
