<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE concept PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA Concept//EN" "technicalContent/dtd/concept.dtd" [
]>



<concept id = "id168D8A00AW6"
    xmlns:ditaarch = "http://dita.oasis-open.org/architecture/2005/">
<title>Introduction</title>
<prolog><author>anamika sharma</author>
<metadata><keywords><keyword>Quick Union</keyword></keywords></metadata></prolog>
<conbody><p>The 3 in. 15k, Quick Union provides a safe and fast
method of making up the flow head and landing joint to the main
landing string without rotation of the flow head assembly or damaging
the premium connection.</p>
<p>The 3 in. 15k, Quick Union manual contains maintenance procedures and
applies to 101901873. A separate Maintenance Check Sheet (DBT-QU-MNT-3500.MCS)
is required to be completed for all equipment maintenance. The user
should review technology bulletins, tool alerts, locate the MCS
and drawing (DBT-QU-3500). For any additional information, questions, or
concerns contact Testing and Subsea (TSS) Global Technical Advisor.</p>
<note><p>After a job, the tool must be completely disassembled and cleaned.
Visually inspect all tool components per ST-GL-HAL-SSS-510. Any component
that does not meet the visual inspection acceptance criteria must
be replaced. All Single Cycle tools must be operated/functioned
if this has not occurred previously. All Multi Cycle tools must
be functioned to the appropriate disassemble position as directed
in the manual to enable the disassembly of the tool. Consult the
Global Maintenance Standard for Subsea on the inspection interval
requirements and general maintenance standards. Record all components
and elastomers replaced in the assembly on the Maintenance Check
Sheet (DBT-QU-MNT-3500.MCS), and include all trace or batch numbers.
All component trace or batch numbers must be additionally captured
on the trace log sheet. For additional questions or concerns, contact
the relevant TSS Global Technical Advisor.</p></note></conbody>
<related-links>
<link href = "Pre_Maintenance_Preparation.xml#id168DAI0009W"
    outputclass = "fm:DITA Default Format"><linktext >Chapter 2:
Pre Maintenance Preparation</linktext></link>
<link href = "Maintenance_Assembly.xml#id168DB100SFR"
    outputclass = "DITA Default Format"><linktext >Maintenance Assembly</linktext></link></related-links></concept>
